http://www.rockymountainhardware.com/privacy

Privacy
This Privacy Policy explains Rocky Mountain Hardware's policy regarding the privacy of information supplied by users or collected by us from users of Rocky Mountain Hardware's website. We are committed to protecting your privacy.  By using our website, you consent to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy, including the collection and use of your personal information as described herein.
Changes in this Privacy Policy
This Policy may change over time as we modify or expand our service; we suggest that you check back from time to time in order to understand how we treat your information.
Links to Other Sites
The rockymountainhardware.com website may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting the websites. We have no responsibility for linked websites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
What Information is Being Collected
Information voluntarily submitted by users:  Rocky Mountain Hardware collects certain information from and about its users. Various forms require users to give us contact information. Not all information is required to be provided (required information will be clearly noted), but if you should choose to withhold information, you may not be eligible to participate in or receive full benefit from all products or services on the website.
Information automatically collected from users:  When you visit this (or any other) website, your browser automatically transmits certain information including the type of computer, operating system and web browser you are using. We may also automatically collect information including your IP address, the web pages you visit on our site, and the date and time of your visit.
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.  Your browser may permit you to change settings to prevent the acceptance of cookies, but if you choose to do so certain web pages may not function properly.
Our Use of Your Information
We may use your information to provide personalized content and services. Any account information you supply will be used only to process the requested transaction or to contact you regarding a specific inquiry or transaction. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this Privacy Policy. You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number below.
Third Party Distribution of Your Information
Rocky Mountain Hardware does not sell, rent, license or otherwise provide any individually identifiable information to any third parties.  Except as specifically stated below, Rocky Mountain Hardware will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about its users to any third party without first receiving that user's permission.  Rocky Mountain Hardware may disclose your information to comply with any law, regulation, subpoena or court order, or to protect or enforce our legal rights.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, such as firewalls and authentication protection. This website, and more importantly all user information, is further protected by a multi-layer firewall based security system.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
© 2020 Rocky Mountain Hardware, Inc.      888.788.2013 (+00 1.208.788.2013)
